Finding Aid for School of Dentistry (University of Michigan) Records, 1873-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archived Dental School Website
  The Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Dentistry. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1996 as well as captures provided by Bentley Library archivists in 2002, 2003, and 2008. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Archived School of Dentistry home page, 1996-[ongoing]
    - 1996-[ONGOING]
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - June 23, 2003, .ZIP file
    - May 15, 2008, .ZIP file
    - Archived School of Dentistry home page, 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the School of Dentistry, 2010-[ongoing]
Related Material
Miscellaneous material from the dental fraternity Delta Sigma Delta, including artifacts and photographs, are located in the Delta Sigma Delta Room at the Bentley Historical Library.